{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2af3,
  type: '选择题',
  tips: '知识点04',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目pkxlRI3',
  answer: '答案lsvdUV3' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1924,
  type: '选择题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目gsjkCIWC4',
  answer: '答案vvklxSI7' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d22d5,
  type: '选择题',
  tips: '知识点41',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目lddvokUCY7',
  answer: '答案ydHPB8' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1fe6,
  type: '选择题',
  tips: '知识点30',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目sucwjfQYN6',
  answer: '答案vuYDS4' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d238d,
  type: '简答题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目qcURXM5',
  answer: '答案zYV9' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1abf,
  type: '简答题',
  tips: '知识点04',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目lbxIZNR5',
  answer: '答案vIDHLS6' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2314,
  type: '简答题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目hTI3',
  answer: '答案bwsgUJWJG7' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d17aa,
  type: '选择题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '中' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d3231,
  type: '判断题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目hOE7',
  answer: '答案zsDSPS7' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2572,
  type: '判断题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目hpQNJ7',
  answer: '答案uDR8' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1b1d,
  type: '简答题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目vbVIYYK4',
  answer: '答案yqgvxEXT5' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1288,
  type: '判断题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目jxpcvuPO1',
  answer: '答案rtwjWLP7' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2866,
  type: '简答题',
  tips: '知识点41',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目mdXL2',
  answer: '答案zbBIN6' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1a18,
  type: '简答题',
  tips: '知识点30',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目coG4',
  answer: '答案angkeKJV6' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2f0a,
  type: '解答题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目hemGYZ2',
  answer: '答案wwyeebnaL9' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d25be,
  type: '填空题',
  tips: '知识点41',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目koSREY2',
  answer: '答案yfdewzFF6' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d11e4,
  type: '判断题',
  tips: '知识点30',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目pyfKA3',
  answer: '答案odsgIEKQO8' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d28c7,
  type: '判断题',
  tips: '知识点41',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目qtlWRQAR2',
  answer: '答案zklRADC7' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d3310,
  type: '解答题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目sYQ7',
  answer: '答案lpcqySDOMCD9' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d288e,
  type: '填空题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目xgsBMCOWRM6',
  answer: '答案tphLY6' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d214f,
  type: '判断题',
  tips: '知识点04',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目hdwryGJF2',
  answer: '答案smxCTJKH7' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d30e9,
  type: '解答题',
  tips: '知识点41',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目twgCQV6',
  answer: '答案gYLH1' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d0eac,
  type: '解答题',
  tips: '知识点30',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目oqwIWVNN7',
  answer: '答案lojiBGSK5' },,{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2327,
  type: '解答题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目csoYPJ7',
  answer: '答案dlvjlCJ3' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d335d,
  type: '填空题',
  tips: '知识点20',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目rHB4',
  answer: '答案vumsmERVBSRM5' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d16ad,
  type: '解答题',
  tips: '知识点04',
  level: '易',
  question: '题目dfprTEC8',
  answer: '答案ziiV9' },,{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2d52,
  type: '填空题',
  tips: '知识点09',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目cgnPNMYQDJ7',
  answer: '答案bkhZRIVMLC8' },{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d2589,
  type: '填空题',
  tips: '知识点04',
  level: '难',
  question: '题目kFHTB8',
  answer: '答案rbnFZE4' },,,,{ _id: 5879c86b1acfbf6cd73d1402,
  type: '填空题',
  tips: '知识点30',
  level: '中',
  question: '题目rcgXF6',
  answer: '答案uxZXU5' },